Let's talk about how to stick your opponent with taking the queen of spades, or risking taking the queen of spades.
Let's look at this hand right here, with the knowledge, and this is important, with the knowledge that I passed my opponent the queen of spades.
When we passed three, I passed my opponent the queen of spades.
Okay?
That being said, what I want to do is I want to lead off, when clubs are led, when that deuce of clubs is going around, I want to lead off with this ace of clubs to guarantee that I take the trick.
And then I want to play my highest spade that does not outrank a queen.
And then the next time, I want to play my highest spade that does not outrank the queen.
And pretty soon, the guy that I passed the queen of spades to is going to be forced to play it.
And the reason is, there is a finite number of spades in a deck of cards, right?
There are thirteen, and I hold six of them, six.
So there's only seven left, and one of them is that queen.
So there's only six left that aren't the queen of spade.
So if I lead spades twice, statistically speaking, on the second time, if it didn't happen on the first time, on the second time the guy I passed the queen of spades to is going to be forced to play it.